<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts - Category - pwnland</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/posts/</link>
        <description>Posts - Category - pwnland</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>jadenwijata@gmail.com (xenonminer)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>jadenwijata@gmail.com (xenonminer)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Offensive Certifications Part 1</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/offensive-certifications/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Xenonminer</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/offensive-certifications/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<h1 id="introduction">Introduction</h1>
<p>In the past 6 months, I have been working on and achieved 3 certifications related to offensive security. The 3 certifications are Certified Penetration Testing Specialist (CPTS), Certified Bug Bounty Hunter (CBBH), and Certified Red Team Operator (CRTO) from HackTheBox and Zero-Point Security. This blog post will be detailing my experiences through these certifications and as a comparison.</p>
<h2 id="cpts">CPTS</h2>
<p>The Certified Penetration Testing Specialist (CPTS) certification was the first certification I achieved. The certification was a great introduction to pentesting web and network applications.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Scorpio Linux Setup</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/scorpio-linux-setup/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Xenonminer</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/scorpio-linux-setup/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<h1 id="description">Description</h1>
<p>In this blog post, you will learn how to setup the <a href="https://github.com/troy-cyber/scorpio" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Scorpio Scoring Engine</a> for Linux OSes.</p>
<h2 id="what-is-scorpio">What is Scorpio?</h2>
<p>Scorpio is a Python-based scoring engine created to score image vulnerabilities. Scorpio checks if a vulnerability has been fixed and gives live feedback to the students.</p>
<h2 id="how-does-scorpio-work">How does Scorpio work?</h2>
<p>The image creator (you) will implement vulnerabilities onto a virtual machine and record them onto <strong>engine.py</strong> which runs every 30 seconds. As the students secure the system, the scoring engine will update <strong>Template.html</strong> (Scoring Report) to display the fixed vulnerabilities.</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
